Guide to the Duke University Progress Pictures Collection, 1925-1932 UA.01.15.0012
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- West Campus, 1927-1932
  - West Campus Progress Picture #195, 1929 May 3 (Box 3, Print WC195)
    From back of photo: "View taken from near center of Main Quadrangle showing Union Building Tower."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #196, 1929 May 3 (Box 3, Print WC196)
    From back of photo: "View taken from Chapel location, showing Class Room and Auditorium Building, with Union Building at left."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #197, 1929 May 3 (Box 3, Print WC197)
    From back of photo: "View taken from near Chapel location, showing School of Religion and Library."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #198, 1929 May 3 (Box 3, Print WC198)
    From back of photo: "View showing Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle], with foundation for Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle] in foreground."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #199, 1929 May 3 (Box 3, Print WC199)
    From back of photo: "View taken from the foundation of Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle], showing Group 'A' Dormitory [Craven Quadrangle]. The Medical School can be seen in the upper left hand corner of picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #200, 1929 May 3 (Box 3, Print WC200)
    From back of photo: "View taken from open end of Horseshoe at [Wallace Wade] Stadium, showing grading completed and concrete work started."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #201, 1929 May 3 (Box 3, Print WC201)
    From back of photo: "View showing the [Wallace Wade] Stadium, taken from closed end of Horseshoe."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #202, 1929 May 3 (Box 3, Print WC202)
    From back of photo: "View showing location for [Card] Gymnasium"
  - West Campus Progress Picture #203, 1929 June 1 (Box 3, Print WC203)
    From back of photo: "View of entrance to Medical School."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #204, 1929 June 1 (Box 3, Print WC204)
    From back of photo: "View taken from main quadrangle showing front of Library and Law Building [now Languages Building]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #205, 1929 June 1 (Box 3, Print WC205)
    From back of photo: "View taken from main quadrangle showing the Union Building and Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle] at left of picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #206, 1929 June 1 (Box 3, Print WC206)
    From back of photo: "View taken from outside of quadrangle showing Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle] in the foreground, with Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle] at left of picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #207, 1929 June 1 (Box 3, Print WC207)
    From back of photo: "View taken from outside of quadrangle showing foundation of Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle], with Group 'A' Dormitory [Craven Quadrangle] in the background."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #208, 1929 June 1 (Box 3, Print WC208)
    From back of photo: "View taken from location of Chapel showing School of Religion and Library Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #209, 1929 June 1 (Box 3, Print WC209)
    From back of photo: "View taken from Chapel location showing Class Room and Auditorium Building and Union Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #210, 1929 June 1 (Box 3, Print WC210)
    From back of photo: "[Wallace Wade] Stadium - View taken from open end of Stadium, showing playing field and walls around same."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #211, 1929 June 1 (Box 3, Print WC211)
    From back of photograph: "[Wallace Wade] Stadium - View taken from closed end of the horseshoe showing playing field and wall around same. On the left can be seen stepping for seat bank."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #212, 1929 June 1 (Box 3, Print WC212)
    From back of photograph: "View showing concreting foundation for [Card] Gymnasium."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #213, 1929 June 8 (Box 3, Print WC213)
    From back of photograph: "View showing [Wallace Wade] Stadium, taken from the southwest end of the horseshoe."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #214, 1929 June 8 (Box 3, Print WC214)
    View from back of photograph: "View showing the [Wallace Wade] Stadium, taken from open end of horseshoe."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #215, 1929 July 1 (Box 3, Print WC215)
    From back of photograph: 'View showing front of the Medical School."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #216, 1929 July 1 (Box 3, Print WC216)
    From back of photograph: "View showing the campus front of the Law Building [now Languages Building] and Library."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #217, 1929 July 1 (Box 3, Print WC217)
    From back of photograph: "View showing campus front of the Union Building, with Group 'C' Dormitories at left and Auditorium at right of picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #218, 1929 July 1 (Box 3, Print WC218)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from rear of Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle] showing Group 'B' and Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #219, 1929 July 1 (Box 3, Print WC219)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from rear of Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle] showing Group 'A' [Craven Quadrangle] and Group 'B' Dormitories."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #220, 1929 July 1 (Box 3, Print WC220)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Chapel location showing School of Religion and Library Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #221, 1929 July 1 (Box 3, Print WC221)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from near Chapel location showing Auditorium and Union Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #222A, 1929 July 1 (Box 3, Print WC222a)
    From back of photograph: "View showing [Wallace Wade] Stadium."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #222B, 1929 July 1 (Box 3, Print WC222b)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #223, 1929 July 1 (Box 3, Print WC223)
    From back of photograph: "View showing [Wallace Wade] Stadium, taken from top of seats."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #224, 1929 July 1 (Box 3, Print WC224)
    From back of photograph: "View showing foundation of [Card] Gymnasium Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #225, 1929 July 23 (Box 3, Print WC225)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from fountain location, looking along main entrance road toward Chapel."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #226, 1929 July 23 (Box 3, Print WC226)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from intersection of main and Chapel axis, looking along entrance road toward fountain."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #227, 1929 July 23 (Box 3, Print WC227)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from intersection of main and Chapel axis, looking toward Chapel site."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #228, 1929 July 23 (Box 3, Print WC228)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Medical School showing Chemistry Building site. Law Building [now Languages Building] and Library in the center of the picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #229, 1929 July 23 (Box 3, Print WC229)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Medical School Building showing location of Botany and Zoology Building [now Sociology-Psychology Building] at left of picture and location of Chemistry Building where logs are piled at right hand edge of picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #230, 1929 July 23 (Box 3, Print WC230)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from road at the rear of the Auditorium, showing court between Union Building and Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #231, 1929 July 23 (Box 3, Print WC231)
    From back of photograph: "View showing construction of the seat banks for the [Wallace Wade] Stadium. At right of picture shows foundation excavated ready for concrete. Next - Steel form in place and men pouring concrete. Next - To the left, the finished wooden seats being placed on concrete. At the upper center of picture, near the pole, shows location of Guest Box."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #232, 1929 July 29 (Box 3, Print WC232)
    From back of photograph: "View showing front of Medical School facing Quadrangle."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #233, 1929 July 29 (Box 3, Print WC233)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from center of Quadrangle showing Union Building, Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle] and part of the Auditorium Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #234, 1929 July 29 (Box 3, Print WC234)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Quadrangle showing Law Building [now Languages Building] and Library."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #235, 1929 July 29 (Box 3, Print WC235)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from court and of Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle], showing part of Group 'B' Dormitory and Group 'C' Dormitory [Kilgo Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #236, 1929 July 29 (Box 3, Print WC236)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from court end of Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle] showing part of Group 'B' Dormitory and Group 'A' Dormitory [Craven Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #237, 1929 July 29 (Box 3, Print WC237)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from rear of Group 'A' Dormitory [Craven Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #238, 1929 July 29 (Box 3, Print WC238)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from rear of Auditorium Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #239, 1929 July 29 (Box 3, Print WC239)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Chapel location showing School of Religion and Library."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #240, 1929 July 29 (Box 3, Print WC240)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Chapel location showing classroom and Auditorium Building and Union Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #241, 1929 July 29 (Box 3, Print WC241)
    From back of photograph: "View showing first floor of [Card] Gymnasium ready for concreting."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #242, 1929 July 29 (Box 3, Print WC242)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Medical School showing location of Botany and Zoology Building [now Sociology-Psychology Building] and Physics Building [now Social Sciences Building]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #243, 1929 July 29 (Box 3, Print WC243)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #244A, 1929 July 29 (Box 3, Print WC244a)
    From back of photograph: "View showing [Wallace Wade] Stadium, taken from open end of horseshoe."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #244B, 1929 July 29 (Box 3, Print WC244b)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #245, 1929 September 3 (Box 3, Print WC245)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from location of Chapel, showing School of Religion."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #246, 1929 September 3 (Box 3, Print WC246)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from location of Chapel, showing Classroom and Auditorium and Union Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #247, 1929 September 3 (Box 3, Print WC247)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from south end of Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle], showing 'B' Dormitory and shovel excavating for the extension to Group 'B'."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #248, 1929 September 3 (Box 3, Print WC248)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from in front of Medical School and Hospital, showing foundation work for Botany and Zoology Building [Sociology-Psychology Building]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #249, 1929 September 3 (Box 3, Print WC249)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from rear of Group 'A' Dormitory [Craven Quadrangle]. The blank wall shows where Group 'A' Dormitory extension joins same. Excavation for this shown in foreground."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #250, 1929 September 3 (Box 3, Print WC250)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from rear of classroom and Auditorium, showing location of stage. Union Building at right of picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #251, 1929 September 3 (Box 3, Print WC251)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from the main entrance, showing front of Library and Law Building [now Languages Building]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #252, 1929 September 3 (Box 3, Print WC252)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from front of [Card] Gymnasium, showing part of steel trusses for erection of Gymnasium."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #253, 1929 September 3 (Box 3, Print WC253)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from south end of Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle], showing Group 'A' [Craven Quadrangle] and 'B' Dormitories. Medical School can be seen through railway gap."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #254, 1929 September 3 (Box 3, Print WC254)
    From back of photograph: "View of the [Wallace Wade] Stadium."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #255A, 1929 September 3 (Box 3, Print WC255a)
    From back of photograph: "View of the [Wallace Wade] Stadium, taken from open end of horseshoe."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #255B, 1929 September 3 (Box 3, Print WC255b)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #256, 1929 October 4 (Box 3, Print WC256)
    From back of photograph: "Union Building and Classroom and Auditorium Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #256, 1929 October 4 (Box 3, Print WC257)
    From back of photograph: "View showing foundation for extension to Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #258, 1929 October 4 (Box 3, Print WC258)
    From back of photograph: "View showing foundation for extension to Group 'A' Dormitory [Craven Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #259, 1929 October 4 (Box 3, Print WC259)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #260, 1929 October 4 (Box 3, Print WC260)
    From back of photograph: "View showing front of the [Card] Gymnasium Building.'
  - West Campus Progress Picture #261, 1929 October 4 (Box 3, Print WC261)
    From back of photograph: "View showing the rear of classroom and Auditorium Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #262, 1929 October 4 (Box 3, Print WC262)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #263, 1929 October 4 (Box 3, Print WC263)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Chapel location showing Classroom and Auditorium and Union Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #264, 1929 October 4 (Box 3, Print WC264)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from near front of Medical School and showing Botany and Zoology Building [now Sociology-Psychology Building]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #265, 1929 October 4 (Box 3, Print WC265)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #266A, 1929 October 4 (Box 3, Print WC266a)
    From back of photograph: "View showing [Wallace Wade] Stadium completed."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #266B, 1929 October 4 (Box 3, Print WC266b)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #267, 1929 November 8 (Box 3, Print WC267)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Medical School and Hospital showing Botany and Zoology Building [now Sociology-Psychology Building]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #268, 1929 November 8 (Box 3, Print WC268)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from main Quadrangle showing Law Building [now Languages Building], Library and Union Building at extreme left."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #269, 1929 November 8 (Box 3, Print WC269)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Chapel location, showing Auditorium Building and Union Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #270, 1929 November 8 (Box 3, Print WC270)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Chapel location, showing School of Religion and Library."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #271, 1929 November 8 (Box 3, Print WC271)
    From back of photograph: "View showing rear of Classroom and Auditorium Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #272, 1929 November 8 (Box 3, Print WC272)
    From back of photograph: "View showing front of [Card] Gymnasium Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #273, 1929 November 8 (Box 3, Print WC273)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from main Quadrangle showing front of Group 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #274, 1929 November 8 (Box 3, Print WC274)
    From back of photograph: "View showing rear of Group 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #275, 1929 November 8 (Box 3, Print WC275)
    From back of photograph: "View showing rear of Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle] and Group 'B' Dormitories extension."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #276, 1929 November 8 (Box 3, Print WC276)
    From back of photograph: "View showing rear of Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle] and also foundation in front of picture for Group 'B' Dormitories extension."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #277, 1929 November 8 (Box 3, Print WC277)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from main Quadrangle showing Group 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle] on left and Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle] on the right of picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #278, 1929 November 8 (Box 3, Print WC278)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from location of Physics Building [now Social Sciences Building], showing Medical School and Hospital, with Botany and Zoology Building [now Sociology-Psychology Building] in foreground."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #279, 1929 December 4 (Box 3, Print WC279)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Medical School and Hospital, showing Botany and Zoology Building [now Sociology-Psychology Building] on the left, and Library, Union Building and Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle] on the right."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #280, 1929 December 4 (Box 3, Print WC280)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Library showing Botany and Zoology Building [now Sociology-Psychology Building] and Medical School."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #281, 1929 December 4 (Box 3, Print WC281)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from location of Physics Building [now Social Sciences Building], showing Law Building [Languages Building] and Library Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #282, 1929 December 4 (Box 3, Print WC282)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Chapel location showing Auditorium Building and Union Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #283, 1929 December 4 (Box 3, Print WC283)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #284, 1929 December 4 (Box 3, Print WC284)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from rear of Auditorium showing stage under construction, and Union Building at right."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #285, 1929 December 4 (Box 3, Print WC285)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #286, 1929 December 4 (Box 3, Print WC286)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from the south end of Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle] showing Group 'B' Dormitories under construction."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #287, 1929 December 4 (Box 3, Print WC287)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from southeast corner of Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle] extension showing court at Group 'B' Dormitories."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #288, 1929 December 4 (Box 3, Print WC288)
    From back of photograph: "View showing construction of the first floor for Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle] extension."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #289, 1929 December 4 (Box 3, Print WC289)
    From back of photograph: "View showing the end of Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle] and rear of Group 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle]. Derrick is located in Group 'A' Dormitories extension court."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #290, 1929 December 4 (Box 3, Print WC290)
    From back of photograph: "View showing rear of Group 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle] and Group 'A' Dormitories extension."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #291, 1929 December 4 (Box 3, Print WC291)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from the front of Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle] showing front of Group 'A' [Craven Quadrangle] and Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #292, 1929 December 4 (Box 3, Print WC292)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from third floor of Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle] showing front of Group 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle], with Medical School and Hospital at the left."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #293, 1930 January 2 (Box 3, Print WC293)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Medical School looking south along main Quadrangle."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #294, 1930 January 2 (Box 3, Print WC294)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from near front of Law Building [now Languages Building], showing Botany and Zoology Building [now Sociology-Psychology Building] and Medical School."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #295, 1930 January 2 (Box 3, Print WC295)
    From back of photograph: "View showing front of Law Building [now Languages Building]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #296, 1930 January 2 (Box 3, Print WC296)
    From back of photograph: "View showing front of Library."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #297, 1930 January 2 (Box 3, Print WC297)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from near end of Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle], showing extension for Group 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #298, 1930 January 2 (Box 3, Print WC298)
    From back of photograph: "View showing extension for Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #299, 1930 January 2 (Box 3, Print WC299)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #300, 1930 January 2 (Box 3, Print WC300)
    From back of photograph: "View showing rear of Classroom and Auditorium Building, showing stage under construction."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #301, 1930 January 2 (Box 4, Print WC301)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from location of Chapel showing School of Religion and Library."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #302, 1930 January 2 (Box 4, Print WC302)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #303, 1930 January 2 (Box 4, Print WC303)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from front of Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle], showing front of Group 'A' [Craven Quadrangle] and 'B' [Crowell Quadrangle] Dormitories."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #304, 1930 January 2 (Box 4, Print WC304)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from center of Quadrangle near Union Building showing front of Group 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #305A, 1930 January 2 (Box 4, Print WC305a)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from south end of Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle] showing extension to Group 'B' Dormitories."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #305B, 1930 January 2 (Box 4, Print WC305b)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #306, 1930 February 5 (Box 4, Print WC306)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Medical School, showing Botany and Zoology Building [now Sociology-Psychology Building]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #307, 1930 February 5 (Box 4, Print WC307)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from main quadrangle with Medical School on the left."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #308, 1930 February 5 (Box 4, Print WC308)
    From back of photograph: "View showing foundation for Physics Building [now Social Sciences Building] and also Botany and Zoology Building [now Sociology-Psychology Building] and Medical School."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #309, 1930 February 5 (Box 4, Print WC309)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #310, 1930 February 5 (Box 4, Print WC310)
    From back of photograph: "View showing Library, with Law Building [now Languages Building] at right."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #311, 1930 February 5 (Box 4, Print WC311)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Chapel location showing Classroom and Auditorium Building and Union Building."